{
    "id": "e8fc1e9c56a7416ab3fcdda9570202c4",
    "title": "Tenses Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We ………………… the railway station before the train arrived.",
            "description": "When we talk about two past events, we use the past perfect for the earlier of the two actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "had reached",
                "has reached",
                "reached",
                "was reached"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. here.",
            "description": "We use 'does' when the subject is a singular noun or pronoun. ",
            "answers": [
                "do not live",
                "does not live",
                "does not lives"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... working in the film industry for twenty five years by next January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "will have been",
                "is",
                "would be"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Kumble ………………….. three wickets before rain interrupted the match.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of the two past actions.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "has taken",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. him twice before he left for New York.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of the two past actions.",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Edison ……………… newspapers before he became a highly successful inventor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sold",
                "was selling",
                "has sold"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was young I ..................... out everyday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had worked",
                "worked",
                "was working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… for Singapore this evening.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about future events when the arrangement already exists. ",
            "answers": [
                "are leaving",
                "were leaving",
                "have been leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They ..................... living in this city for twenty years.",
            "description": "We use the present perfect continuous tense to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "have been",
                "had been",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. here for ten years now.",
            "description": "The present perfect tense is also used to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "lived",
                "have lived",
                "had lived"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}